Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Universal Zulu Nation Documents, 1980-2006
  - Infinity Lessons
    - Black Power, Achievement, Thought
      - Infinity lesson on Alkebu-Lan; homeland of all people, Undated (Box 506, Folder 3)
      - Map of Africa, Undated (Box 506, Folder 11)
      - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Bylaws/The Invention of Black America, 1993 (Box 506, Folder 12)
      - The Nigger Syndrome, Undated (Box 506, Folder 13)
      - Not to Be a Nigger, Undated (Box 506, Folder 14)
      - On preserving Black history, 1982 (Box 506, Folder 15)
    - Health, Wellness, and Nutrition
      - Are Drugs Necessary?, Undated; Burton, A. (Box 501, Folder 7)
      - Conigar-The Natural Immune Enhancer, Undated (Box 501, Folder 8)
      - Food Additives in the English Language, Undated (Box 501, Folder 9)
      - The Great Condom Cover-Up, Undated (Box 501, Folder 10)
      - Guide to Fasting, Undated (Box 501, Folder 11)
      - Herbal Aid for Emergencies, Undated (Box 501, Folder 12)
      - The Human Brain, Undated (Box 501, Folder 13)
      - Hygiene Lesson #6 on Breathing and CPR, Undated (Box 501, Folder 14)
      - Infinity Lesson on Water #1/Do "Drugs" or "Medicines" Really Cure You?, Undated (Box 501, Folder 21)
      - Misc. Health/Nutrition, Undated (Box 501, Folder 15)
      - National Condom Week, Undated (Box 501, Folder 16)
      - Pork in Soaps, 1979-08-25 (Box 501, Folder 17)
      - The Pork Worm, Undated (Box 501, Folder 18)
      - The Respiratory System, Undated (Box 501, Folder 19)
      - The Scientific Facts on the Biological Effects of Fluorides #1, Undated (Box 501, Folder 20)
      - Vegetables (Eat), Undated (Box 501, Folder 22)
      - Vitamin/Mineral Sources, Undated (Box 501, Folder 23)
      - Water #1, Undated (Box 501, Folder 24)
    - Latinx Identity
      - The Black and Hispanic Agenda, Undated (Box 500, Folder 1)
      - Don Pedro Albizu Campos, Undated (Box 500, Folder 5)
      - From Tainos to Puerto Ricans, Undated (Box 500, Folder 6)
      - Hispanic Si y No, Undated (Box 500, Folder 14)
      - Infinity Lesson #1 on Puerto Rico, Undated (Box 500, Folder 9)
      - Info on Latin Culture, Undated (Box 500, Folder 13)
      - Khayan Zulu Lessons: Dominican Flag, Undated (Box 500, Folder 2)
      - Khayan Zulu-Puerto Rican Flag, Undated (Box 500, Folder 8)
      - Latin Kings, Undated (Box 500, Folder 7)
      - Memo in Spanish, Undated; Carlos, Frank and Lou Paler (Box 500, Folder 15)
      - On Dominican Republic, Undated (Box 500, Folder 4)
      - On the Dominican Flag, Undated (Box 500, Folder 3)
      - Puerto Rican Studies, Undated (Box 500, Folder 10)
      - We Didn't Drop from the Sky, Undated; Perez, Richard (Box 500, Folder 12)
      - Young Lords, 1993-05 (Box 500, Folder 11)
    - Police
      - A Message on Police Brutality, Undated; Carlos, Frank and Manuel Oguando (Box 501, Folder 3)
      - Essay on the Origins of the Police, Undated (Box 501, Folder 6)
      - Misc. Police, Undated (Box 501, Folder 1)
      - Police Entrapment, Undated (Box 501, Folder 5)
      - What To Do If the Police Stop You for Questioning, Undated (Box 501, Folder 2)
      - What To Do If You Are Arrested or Framed by Police, Undated (Box 501, Folder 4)
    - Religion
      - The 12 Jewels of Islam, Undated (Box 499, Folder 1)
      - A Message from Imam W. Deen Mohammed, Undated; Mohammed, W. Deen (Box 499, Folder 2)
      - A New Global Ethic, 1993-12-17-1993-12-19; Stoltz, Craig (Box 499, Folder 3)
      - Actual Facts, Undated (Box 499, Folder 4)
      - ADL: Mainstreaming Anti-Semitism-The Legitimation of Louis Farrakhan, Undated (Box 499, Folder 5)
      - Blacks in the Bible, Undated (Box 499, Folder 6)
      - The Creation and the Garden of Eden, Undated (Box 499, Folder 7)
      - English Lesson No. 1/Supreme Alphabets and Mathematics, Undated (Box 499, Folder 8)
      - The Founding Fathers, Undated (Box 499, Folder 9)
      - God is Black, Undated (Box 499, Folder 10)
      - History of the Honorable Elijah Muhammad, Undated (Box 499, Folder 11)
      - Infinity Plus Lesson on the 5% Nation, Undated (Box 545, Folder 5)
      - The Influence of the Locusts Expand via Zulu Nation, 2005-01-15 (Box 499, Folder 12)
      - The Lost Word, 1967 (Box 499, Folder 13)
      - Louis Farrakhan, Undated (Box 499, Folder 14)
      - The History of Christmas and the Birth of Jesus Christ, Undated (Box 499, Folder 15)
      - Infinity Lesson on Farrakhan, Undated (Box 499, Folder 16)
      - The Meaning of the Cross, Undated (Box 499, Folder 17)
      - The Mind, Undated (Box 499, Folder 18)
      - Mosques/Islam, Undated (Box 499, Folder 19)
      - Nation of Islam-F.O.I. Training and Lessons, Undated (Box 499, Folder 20)
      - Infinity Lesson of Religious Prayer, Undated (Box 499, Folder 21)
      - The Sun, Undated (Box 499, Folder 22)
      - Supreme Alphabets, Undated (Box 499, Folder 23)
      - Supreme Mathematic, Undated (Box 499, Folder 24)
      - UZN Relationship with the Nation of Islam, Undated; Brother Fabel (Box 499, Folder 25)
      - War Against Black People, Undated (Box 499, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous religion, Undated (Box 500, Folder 166)
    - Sovereign Citizen Movement
      - Charter of the UN, 2001-01-18 (Box 498, Folder 9)
      - Moorish/Islamic Jurisprudence, Undated (Box 498, Folder 4)
      - Non-Tax Liability/Affidavit of Fact, Undated (Box 498, Folder 5)
      - Social Security Numbers, Undated (Box 498, Folder 8)
      - The US Constitution & Fascinating Facts About It, 1998; Tedeschi, Robert F., Jr. (Box 498, Folder 6)
      - Universal Zulu Kemetic Muurs/Moors, Undated (Box 501, Folder 25)
      - What Does This Man Know That You Don't?, Undated (Box 498, Folder 7)
    - Surveillance, Technology, New World Order, and UFOs
      - 666 Mark of the Beast, Undated (Box 507, Folder 1)
      - Abduction & Manipulation of Humans Using Advanced Technology, Undated (Box 507, Folder 3)
      - Alt.Conspiracy Printouts, 1994-1995 (Box 506, Folder 23)
      - Beware of the New World Order, Undated (Box 507, Folder 4)
      - Big Brother/ID Tag, 1990 (Box 507, Folder 5)
      - The Church of Satan Thrives on What You Buy, Undated (Box 507, Folder 6)
      - Executive Orders for a National State of Emergency, Undated (Box 507, Folder 8)
      - How You're Spied On, 1997 (Box 507, Folder 7)
      - Mark of Deception - Mark of the Beast, 1989 (Box 507, Folder 2)
      - Microwaves, Undated (Box 507, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous New World Order/Surveillance, 1989 (Box 507, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous UFOs, 1997 (Box 506, Folder 24)
      - Power of the Mind, Undated (Box 507, Folder 11)
      - The Religion of the New World Order, Undated (Box 507, Folder 12)
      - Signs of the New World Order, Undated (Box 507, Folder 13)
      - Spy Government, 1967 (Box 507, Folder 14)
      - This is a Black Community Bio-Attack Alert, 1989 (Box 507, Folder 16)
      - The TV Junkies, Undated (Box 507, Folder 15)
      - UFOs & Other Info, 1989 (Box 506, Folder 25)
      - Warning to the American People, Undated (Box 507, Folder 17)
      - What "New World"?, Undated (Box 507, Folder 18)
      - You Are Becoming A Galactic Human, Undated (Box 506, Folder 26)
    - General Principles and Beliefs
      - 11 Points of Light, Undated (Box 507, Folder 19)
      - 24 things to remember, Undated (Box 507, Folder 20)
      - A positive force in the world, Undated (Box 507, Folder 21)
      - Bam message to Hip Hop Nation, Undated (Box 507, Folder 22)
      - Belief #5 of the Universal Zulu Nation Infinity Lessons, 1995 (Box 507, Folder 23)
      - Beliefs of the Zulu Nation, Undated (Box 507, Folder 24)
      - The Beliefs of the Universal Zulu Nation (French), Undated (Box 507, Folder 25)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Call to Members, 2000 (Box 507, Folder 26)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Charter, Undated (Box 507, Folder 27)
      - Charter Signature, Undated (Box 507, Folder 28)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Chapter Leader Membership Papers, Undated (Box 507, Folder 29)
      - Constitution of the Universal Zulu Nation, Undated (Box 507, Folder 30)
      - Laws and Regulations of the Universal Zulu Nation #2, Undated (Box 507, Folder 31)
      - Laws of Success, Undated (Box 507, Folder 32)
      - Message to the People, Undated (Box 507, Folder 33)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Reading List, Undated (Box 507, Folder 34)
      - Rules & Regulations, Undated (Box 507, Folder 35)
      - Shaka, Undated (Box 507, Folder 36)
      - Shaka Zulu Security, Undated (Box 507, Folder 37)
      - The True Meaning of Hip Hop Culture, Undated (Box 508, Folder 1)
      - The Universal Prayer of the Universal Zulu Nation of this Planet So Called Earth, Undated (Box 508, Folder 2)
      - The Wisdom and Understanding of the Fifteen Beliefs of the Universal Zulu Nation, Undated (Box 508, Folder 3)
      - Zulu Kings, Undated (Box 508, Folder 4)
      - Zulu Laws & Regulations, Undated (Box 508, Folder 5)
      - Zulu Nation Introduction, Undated (Box 508, Folder 6)
      - Zulu Queens, Undated (Box 508, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Infinity Files
      - Blank Passport Applications, 1989 (Box 509, Folder 6)
      - Boycott Crazy Horse Malt Liquor, Undated (Box 509, Folder 5)
      - Capitalism & Money, Undated (Box 509, Folder 4)
      - Cush: Ethiopia, Undated (Box 508, Folder 20)
      - Handouts for members, Undated (Box 508, Folder 13)
      - Infinity Lesson #1-2, Undated (Box 508, Folder 9)
      - Infinity Lesson #1-7, Undated (Box 508, Folder 10)
      - Infinity Lesson #2: Bambaataa (1865-1906 AD), Undated (Box 509, Folder 1)
      - Infinity Lessons, 1973-1982 (Box 508, Folder 14)
      - Infinity Lessons & Communications, Undated (Box 508, Folder 16)
      - Infinity lessons, rules, history, mission, 1990 (Box 508, Folder 11)
      - Lester's World Comic, Undated (Box 509, Folder 8)
      - Lost Civilizations & Global Catastrophes, Undated (Box 508, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous Infinity Lessons, 2004 (Box 508, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Universal Zulu Nation, 1987-2005 (Box 509, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous Universal Zulu Nation files, Undated (Box 508, Folder 15)
      - Mizraim: Egypt, Undated (Box 508, Folder 19)
      - Nazis in NY?, 1993-2005 (Box 508, Folder 17)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Ephemera, 1995 (Box 509, Folder 3)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Master Copies, Undated (Box 508, Folder 12)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Promotion Photo, Undated (Box 509, Folder 10)
      - You Can't Stop Our Culture! Graffiti & Hip Hop!, Undated (Box 509, Folder 7)
      - Zulu Art Work, 1993-1994 (Box 509, Folder 9)
  - Administration
    - Events
      - Chrome Awards, 1995-1996 (Box 509, Folder 18)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 16th Anniversary promotional handouts, 1990 (Box 509, Folder 12)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 19th Anniversary, 1993 (Box 509, Folder 13)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 20th Anniversary, 1994 (Box 509, Folder 14)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 20th Anniversary Sponsorship, Undated (Box 509, Folder 15)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 21st Anniversary Participants, 1995 (Box 509, Folder 16)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 22nd Anniversary, 1996 (Box 509, Folder 19)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 27th Anniversary, Undated (Box 509, Folder 20)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 28th Anniversary/27th Anniversary of the Hip Hop Culture, 2001-2002 (Box 510, Folder 1)
      - Universal Zulu Nation 30th Anniversary, 2003 (Box 510, Folder 2)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Anniversary Faxes, 1995 (Box 509, Folder 17)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Event Flyers, 1994-2003 (Box 509, Folder 11)
    - Public Statements
      - Annual Dues Notice, Undated (Box 510, Folder 3)
      - Book of Stamps Letter, Undated (Box 510, Folder 4)
      - Chaka Freeman Letter to Universal Zulu Nation - Chapter Heads, Undated (Box 510, Folder 5)
      - Club Owner Letter, 1994-1995 (Box 510, Folder 6)
      - Letter from Bambaataa to Universal Zulu Nation Members on Cash Transactions (Box 510, Folder 7)
      - Message to All Universal Zulu Nation Leaders, Members, & Others, Undated (Box 510, Folder 10)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Letter to New York Police Department (Box 510, Folder 8)
      - Universal Zulu Nation memo to parents & community members, Undated (Box 510, Folder 9)
      - Universal Zulu Nation: We Are Not A Violent Street Gang (master copy), Undated (Box 510, Folder 11)
      - Zulu News - Washington, D.C., 1995-02 (Box 510, Folder 12)
      - Zulu News Letters, Undated (Box 510, Folder 14)
      - Zulu News Writers Lessons, Undated (Box 510, Folder 13)
    - Order Forms and Administrative Files
      - Almighty Management Stationary, Undated (Box 511, Folder 2)
      - Art samples from Shaaya Invasion, Undated (Box 546, Folder 12)
      - Cassette Catalogs, Undated (Box 510, Folder 16)
      - Go Go Funk - Washington, D.C., Undated (Box 510, Folder 20)
      - Infinity Lesson Booklist I - #1-#75, Undated (Box 510, Folder 21)
      - Infinity Lesson Booklist II - #76-#128, Undated (Box 510, Folder 22)
      - Universal Zulu Nation - Music Cassette Catalog, Undated (Box 510, Folder 24)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Badges, Undated (Box 511, Folder 3)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Cassette Catalog, Undated (Box 510, Folder 17)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Cassette Catalog - As Sayyid Al Imaam Isa Al Haadi Al Mahdi, Undated (Box 510, Folder 18)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Cassette Catalog of Speeches, Undated (Box 510, Folder 19)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Cassette Catalog on Minister Louis Farrakhan Speeches, Undated (Box 510, Folder 23)
      - Universal Zulu Nation Order Form, 1991 (Box 510, Folder 15)
      - Universal Zulu Nation, Black Membership Forms, Undated (Box 511, Folder 4)
      - UZN - blank membership form in Spanish, Undated (Box 511, Folder 5)
      - UZN Membership Application, Undated (Box 511, Folder 6)
      - Zulu Nation Stationary, Undated (Box 511, Folder 1)
    - UZN Chapters and Operations
      - Belgium Chapter, 1999 (Box 511, Folder 13)
      - Chapter Leaders, Undated (Box 511, Folder 8)
      - Civil Court Lawyer for UZN, 1995 (Box 512, Folder 5)
      - For Zulu Staff Only, 1993 (Box 512, Folder 2)
      - Incorporation of UZN, 2003 (Box 512, Folder 21)
      - Italian Zulu Nation, 1988 (Box 512, Folder 22)
      - The Zulu Nation Chapter Leaders, Undated (Box 511, Folder 10)
      - UZN - Lucky Strike N.Y. (Chapter Membership), 1995 (Box 524, Folder 6)
      - UZN - organizational chart, Undated (Box 511, Folder 7)
      - UZN - Proposed Restructuring, Undated (Box 511, Folder 9)
      - UZN Applicants I, 2000 (Box 512, Folder 6)
      - UZN Applicants II, 1995-1996 (Box 512, Folder 7)
      - UZN Chapter 24 Notes, Undated (Box 512, Folder 1)
      - UZN Chapter Notes/Memos, 1995 (Box 511, Folder 12)
      - UZN DC Chapter, Undated (Box 512, Folder 3)
      - UZN Packet - New Haven, Connecticut, Undated (Box 512, Folder 4)
      - Zulu Nation - Internal Forms, Undated (Box 511, Folder 11)
    - Mail
      Contains incoming mail for the Universal Zulu Nation. Also includes some incoming personal mail for Bambaataa.
      - 1980-1990 (Box 543, Folder 1)
      - 1991 (Box 543, Folder 2)
      - 1993 (Box 543, Folder 3)
      - 1994 (Box 543, Folder 4)
      - 1995 (Box 543, Folder 5)
      - 1996 (Box 543, Folder 6)
      - 1997 (Box 543, Folder 7)
      - 1998 (Box 543, Folder 8)
      - 1999 (Box 543, Folder 9)
      - 2000 (Box 544, Folder 1)
      - 2001 (Box 544, Folder 2)
      - 2002 (Box 544, Folder 3)
      - 2003 (Box 544, Folder 4)
      - 2004 (Box 544, Folder 5)
      - 2005 (Box 544, Folder 6)
      - 2006 (Box 544, Folder 7)
- Stage Costumes and Clothing, Undated
  - Black and gold sequined serpent hat, Undated; MU-2943 (Box 513)
  - Black and gold striped hat, Undated; MU-2944 (Box 513)
  - Silver mask, Undated; MU-2945 (Box 514)
  - Black mask with gold glitter and sequin cord, Undated; MU-2946 (Box 514)
  - Black, gold, and red mask with gold sequin cord, Undated; MU-2947 (Box 514)
  - Black mask with silver glitter and sequin cord, Undated; MU-2948 (Box 514)
  - Wig: straight black hair with silver highlights, Undated; MU-2949 (Box 515)
  - Wig: large Afro, Undated; MU-2950 (Box 515)
  - Dark blue and turquoise hooded jean jacket: Zulu Nation, Undated; MU-2951 (Box 516)
  - Black hoodie: yellow-green, red, black designs, Undated; MU-2952 (Box 516)
  - White t-shirt: Wild style (turquoise, red, yellow, and black), Undated; MU-2953 (Box 517)
  - White t-shirt: Wild style (red, yellow, and black), Undated; MU-2954 (Box 517)
  - White t-shirt: B-Boys Stops Bust, Undated; MU-2955 (Box 517)
  - Brown/beige and plum colored tunic, Undated; MU-2956 (Box 517)
  - Vest--jacket with silver and white 'sun' embroidered on the back, Undated; MU-2957 (Box 517)
  - Black pants with blue waistband, Undated; MU-2958 (Box 517)
  - Light blue sweatpants, Undated; MU-2959 (Box 517)
  - Gold sequined mask with white, blue, yellow, and red feathers, Undated; MU-2960 (Box 518)
  - Vampire cape costume (Charades), Undated; MU-2961 (Box 519)
  - The Wizard costume (Charades), Undated; MU-2962 (Box 519)
  - Gold cape, Undated; MU-2963 (Box 519)
  - Gold cape with collar, Undated; MU-2964 (Box 519)
  - Black tunic with "Bambaataa" lettering and felt applique of raised fists and sun, Undated; MU-2965 (Box 519)
  - Large white robe with patches sewn to each side of chest (Nubian Islamic Hebrews), Undated; MU-2966 (Box 519)
  - Large white robe with light blue cord trim, Undated; MU-2967 (Box 519)
  - Black mask with black and gold feathers, Undated; MU-2968 (Box 520)
  - SHANGO jean jacket, Undated; MU-2969 (Box 521)
  - Gold, black, and blue foam tie and cuffs, Undated; MU-2974 (Box 525)
  - Black velvet collar with gold trim, Undated; MU-2975 (Box 525)
  - Screen printed Egyptian cloth, Undated; MU-2976 (Box 525)
  - Black cape with gold, red, and black chevron stripes, Undated; MU-2977 (Box 525)
  - Dreadlock wig, Undated; MU-2994 (Box 527)
  - Afro wig, Undated; MU-2995 (Box 527)
  - Bat mask, Undated; MU-2996 (Box 528)
  - Embroidered Bambaataa/Zulu Nation felt, Undated; MU-3305-3306 (Box 529)
  - Rings, Undated; MU-3307-3323 (Box 529)
  - Wooden and leather necklaces, Undated; MU-3324-3385 (Box 529)
  - Sunglasses, Undated; MU-3386-3389 (Box 530)
  - Bracelets, Undated; MU-3390-3392 (Box 530)
  - Embroidered wristband, Undated; MU-3393 (Box 530)
  - Jamaica headband, Undated; MU-3394 (Box 530)
  - Woven beanie, Undated; MU-3395 (Box 530)
  - Felt embroidered with Afrika Islam patch, Undated; MU-3396 (Box 530)
  - Carved wooden mask, Undated; MU-3397 (Box 530)
  - Large leather Zulu Nation necklace, Undated; MU-3398 (Box 530)
- Periodicals and Publications, 1955-2007
  - Small Press Publications, 1955-2006
    - Black Power, Achievement, Thought, 1960-2006
      - "Bill of Particulars" Regarding "So-Called" Black History, Undated; Bey, R.V.; Bey, Noble Nature El (Box 512, Folder 8)
      - 300 Names from the Holy Continent, 1983; Osei, G.K. (Box 466, Folder 1)
      - 3D, Undated (Box 486, Folder 25)
      - 666 Baphomet Christ: The Holy Goat, 2003; Epps, S. (Box 466, Folder 2)
      - A Detailed Look at Primary Bab-Els, 2000; Epps, S. (Box 466, Folder 3)
      - A Escravidão Em São Bernardo, Na Colônia E No Império, 1988; Martins, José de Souza (Box 466, Folder 4)
      - A Message of Hope and Deliverance to Grassroots People in Jamaica (and the Caribbean), 1993-09; Farrakhan, Louis (Box 462, Folder 1)
      - A Vida de Zumbi Dos Palmares, 1995-10; Aluno, Caderno do (Box 466, Folder 5)
      - African Heritage Vol. 1, No. 2, 1983 (Box 466, Folder 6)
      - African Mirror Vol. 2, 1979-08-1979-09 (Box 462, Folder 2)
      - The African Origins Book 2, Part 2, Undated; Ashby, Muata (Box 462, Folder 3)
      - The African Origins Book 3, Part 3, Undated; Ashby, Muata (Box 462, Folder 4)
      - African Peoples' Contributions to World Civilizations: Shattering the Myths Vol. 1, 1993; Hamilton, Paul L. (Box 465, Folder 2)
      - Afrikan World Books Trade Catalog, 2004 (Box 462, Folder 5)
      - The Afro-American World Almanac, 1999; Brown, Ross D. (Box 466, Folder 7)
      - Bab-Els: Creation's Unrecognized Power Generators, 2000-2003; Epps, S. (Box 466, Folder 8)
      - Big Black Book, 1988-1989 (Box 466, Folder 9)
      - Big Black Book 9th Annual Edition Vol. 2, 1995 (Box 462, Folder 6)
      - Black Empowerment and Survival Guide, 2000-2003; Epps, S. (Box 466, Folder 10)
      - Black Fist, 2001-09 (Box 466, Folder 11)
      - The Blackman Vol. 1, No. 2, Undated; Garvey, Marcus; Blackman Publishing Co. (Box 462, Folder 7)
        Kingston, Jamaica
      - The Black Man Vol. 6, No. 1, Undated; Garvey, Marcus; Black Man Publishing Co. (Box 462, Folder 8)
        London, England
      - Black Mexico: The Greatest Story Never Told, 2000; Muhammad, Lamont (Box 466, Folder 21)
      - Black News Reprints On Malcolm X, 1986 (Box 466, Folder 12)
      - The Black pages, 1972-1973; Somerville, Raymond (Box 546, Folder 1)
      - The Black Video Guide, 1986 (Box 462, Folder 9)
      - The Children of the Sun, 1981; Parker, George Wells (Box 466, Folder 13)
      - Christopher Columbus and the Afrikan Holocaust, 1993-1998; Clarke, John Henrik (Box 466, Folder 14)
      - Clock of Destiny, 1973 (Box 466, Folder 15)
      - The Colonies of Atlantis, Undated (Box 466, Folder 16)
      - Conscious Rasta Press, 2000-04-01; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 512, Folder 9)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 3, Issue 5, 1996-07; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 462, Folder 11)
        Long Beach, CA
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 3, Issue 6, 1996-08; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 462, Folder 12)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 3, Issue 8, 1996-11; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 1)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 3, No. 1, 1996; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 486, Folder 24)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 3, No. 3, 1996-05; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 462, Folder 10)
        3 copies.
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 4, Issue 1, 1997-01; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 2)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 4, Issue 3, 1997-06; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 3)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 4, No. 4, 1997-08; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 4)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 4, No. 5, 1997-10; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 5)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 5, No. 1, 1998-04; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 6)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 5, No. 2, 1998-05; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 7)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 5, No. 3, 1998-10; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 8)
      - The Conscious Rasta Report Vol. 6, No. 1, 1999-01; Awadu, Keidi Obi; The Conscious Rasta Press (Box 463, Folder 9)
      - Death Angels AKA Zebra Murders, 2005 (Box 463, Folder 10)
      - Elijah Muhammad on African American Education, 1981; Alexander, E. Curtis (Box 467, Folder 1)
      - The Final Call Vol. 18, No. 45, 1999-09-14 (Box 463, Folder 11)
      - Frontline AD 14, 2001-02 (Box 463, Folder 13)
      - Frontline AD 18, 2001-06 (Box 463, Folder 14)
      - Frontline AD 20, 2001-08 (Box 463, Folder 15)
      - Frontline AD 22, 2001-10 (Box 463, Folder 16)
      - Frontline AD 38, 2003-02 (Box 463, Folder 17)
      - Frontline Research Series No. 2, 1998 (Box 463, Folder 12)
      - Funk Anthropology, No. 5, 1983; Boyd, M. (Box 512, Folder 10)